{
    "subject": "resource/Osijek_Oblast",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Osijek",
    "human_readable": "Osijek Oblast has Osijek as its capital.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.987786054611206,
            "question": "Which oblast has Osijek as its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9716652631759644,
            "question": "What is the capital of Osijek Oblast?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9393479228019714,
            "question": "Does Osijek serve as a capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8965126872062683,
            "question": "Are there any other cities within Osijek Oblast besides its capital?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7000554800033569,
            "question": "What is the name of the administrative center of Osijek Oblast?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6978536248207092,
            "question": "Where is Osijek located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.643180251121521,
            "question": "What country is Osijek Oblast a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6025806069374084,
            "question": "Can you provide information about the history of Osijek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5426567792892456,
            "question": "What are some notable features or attractions in Osijek?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48071590065956116,
            "question": "Is Osijek Oblast a region in Croatia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Osijek Oblast has Osijek as its capital.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9130_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable features or attractions in Osijek?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9130_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide information about the history of Osijek?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9130_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is Osijek Oblast a part of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9130_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9130_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9130_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9130_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9130_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9130_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9130_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9130_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9130_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9130_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9130_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that the city of Osijek served as the capital for the Osje\u010dka oblast (Osijek Oblast) during a specified period, which supports the statement that Osijek is or was the capital of Osijek Oblast."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}